[{"questionBody":"Is Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Application :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is IETF :improve :Internet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :transmits :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :transmits :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Error_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Error_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Framing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Framing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Extranet :has :VPN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Extranet :has :VPN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Extranet :has :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Extranet :has :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Active_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Apple_Filing_Protocol :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Apple_Filing_Protocol :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Guided_Media :part_of :Communication_Media ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Brouter :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Brouter :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Brouter :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Brouter :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Brouter :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Modem :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Router :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Switch :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Hub :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Brouter :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Repeater :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Gateway :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Network :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Physical :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is ISO_Standard :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Data_Link :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Session :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Session :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Session :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Session :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Session :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Society :improve :Internet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Flow_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Flow_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Physical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Physical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :transmits :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :transmits :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Error_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Error_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Framing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Framing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :functions :Media_Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :functions :Media_Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Transport :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Presentation :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Class_Fa :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is eMail :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is VOIP :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is RFC :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is eMail :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is VOIP :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is RFC :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Intranet :has :VPN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet :has :VPN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Intranet :has :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet :has :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Malicious_Software :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Modification :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Integrity :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Availablity :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Cryptography :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Passive_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is System_Security :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Confidentiality :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Interception :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Interruption :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Fabrication :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Symmetrie_Encryption :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is SDH :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Ethernet :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching","id":null},{"questionBody":"Is Internet_Protocol :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why No is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching","id":null},{"questionBody":"How many number_of_layers is IP_Suite connected with ?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"4","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why 4 is the correct answer is due to the following : The number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4"},{"id":0,"text":"8","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why 8 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : 8 is multiplies the number_of_layers of IP_Suite and number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4"},{"id":0,"text":"12","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why 12 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : 12 is multiplies the number_of_layers of IP_Suite and number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4"},{"id":0,"text":"16","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why 16 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : 16 is multiplies the number_of_layers of IP_Suite and number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4"}],"strategy":"Datatype-property-based","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why 4 is the correct answer is due to the following : The number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4","id":null},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Bandwidth?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"bw","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why bw is the correct answer is due to the following :bw is Bandwidth"},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why p2 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : p2 is Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why perfo is the incorrect answer is due to the following : perfo is Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why p3 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : p3 is Performance"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with superclasses","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why bw is the correct answer is due to the following :bw is Bandwidth","id":null},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Computer_Networks?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"n1","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why n1 is the correct answer is due to the following :n1 is Computer_Networks"},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why scope is the incorrect answer is due to the following : scope is Scope"},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why sec is the incorrect answer is due to the following : sec is Security"},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why p2 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : p2 is Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why perfo is the incorrect answer is due to the following : perfo is Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why p3 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : p3 is Performance"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with subclasses","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why n1 is the correct answer is due to the following :n1 is Computer_Networks","id":null},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Security?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why sec is the correct answer is due to the following :sec is Security"},{"id":0,"text":"interrr","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why interrr is the incorrect answer is due to the following : interrr is Interruption"},{"id":0,"text":"integ","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why integ is the incorrect answer is due to the following : integ is Integrity"},{"id":0,"text":"confid","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why confid is the incorrect answer is due to the following : confid is Confidentiality"},{"id":0,"text":"modi","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why modi is the incorrect answer is due to the following : modi is Modification"},{"id":0,"text":"availabilty","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why availabilty is the incorrect answer is due to the following : availabilty is Availablity"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with subclasses","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why sec is the correct answer is due to the following :sec is Security","id":null},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Scope?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why scope is the correct answer is due to the following :scope is Scope"},{"id":0,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s4 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s4 is Intranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s3","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s3 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s3 is Intranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s2 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s2 is Internet"},{"id":0,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s1 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s1 is Extranet"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with subclasses","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why scope is the correct answer is due to the following :scope is Scope","id":null},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Extranet?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why s1 is the correct answer is due to the following :s1 is Extranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s4 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s4 is Intranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s3","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s3 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s3 is Intranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s2 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s2 is Internet"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with disjoint sibling classes","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why s1 is the correct answer is due to the following :s1 is Extranet","id":null},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following ia a function of the Bridge?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Translation_Bridge","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Translation_Bridge is the correct answer is due to the following : Translation_Bridge classify_as Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Modem","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Modem is the incorrect answer is due to the following : Modem doesn't classify_as Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Router","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Router is the incorrect answer is due to the following : Router doesn't classify_as Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Switch","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Switch is the incorrect answer is due to the following : Switch doesn't classify_as Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Object-property-based","bloomLvl":"Comprehension","keyFeedback":"The reason why Translation_Bridge is the correct answer is due to the following : Translation_Bridge classify_as Translation_Bridge","id":null},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ Open Systems Interconnection","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"OSI_Model","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why OSI_Model is correct answer is due to the following: OSI_Model Open Systems InterconnectionOSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Flooders","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Flooders is incorrect answer is due to the following: Flooders  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Star_Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Star_Mesh is incorrect answer is due to the following: Star_Mesh  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why CISCO_IOS is incorrect answer is due to the following: CISCO_IOS  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Loaded_TP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Loaded_TP is incorrect answer is due to the following: Loaded_TP  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IP_Suite is incorrect answer is due to the following: IP_Suite  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Bonded_TP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Bonded_TP is incorrect answer is due to the following: Bonded_TP  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Infrared is incorrect answer is due to the following: Infrared  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Scope","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Scope is incorrect answer is due to the following: Scope  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SVOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SVOIP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SVOIP  is Secure Voice over IP"},{"id":0,"text":"Switched","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Switched is incorrect answer is due to the following: Switched  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"ATM_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why ATM_Layer is incorrect answer is due to the following: ATM_Layer  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyOSI_Model is correct answer is due to the following: OSI_Model is  Open Systems Interconnection","id":null},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــRemote Desktop Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is correct answer is due to the following: RDPRemote Desktop ProtocolRDP"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDP  is Session Description Protocol (SDP)"},{"id":0,"text":"LDAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why LDAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: LDAP  is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyRDP is correct answer is due to the following: RDP is Remote Desktop Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــMedia Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is correct answer is due to the following: MGCPMedia Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)MGCP"},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SMTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SMTP  is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol "},{"id":0,"text":"DHCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DHCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: DHCP  is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"CMAC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why CMAC is incorrect answer is due to the following: CMAC  is Cipher-based message authentication code"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyMGCP is correct answer is due to the following: MGCP is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","id":null},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSimple Network Management Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is correct answer is due to the following: SNMPSimple Network Management ProtocolSNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SDM","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDM is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDM  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SFTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SFTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SFTP  is SSH File Transfer Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySNMP is correct answer is due to the following: SNMP is Simple Network Management Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSimple Object Access Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is correct answer is due to the following: SOAPSimple Object Access ProtocolSOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"POP2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP2 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP2  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"POP1","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP1 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP1  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySOAP is correct answer is due to the following: SOAP is Simple Object Access Protocol","id":null},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: 